kotulas.com 2018-08-19

# Privacy Policy

## What does Kotulas.com do with my personal information?

Kotulas.com uses personal information to enhance the overall shopping experience by providing you with better customer service. Positive customer identification allows us to contact the customer and ensure all their needs are met and handled appropriately and accurately. All personal information that we acquire is provided by each individual customer. It is this personal information, given to us by the customer, that allows Kotulas.com to provide knowledgeable support by our customer service team. Benefits you may receive by allowing us to keep your personal information on hand include:

  1. **A Personal Internet Account** — You will be identified by Kotulas.com every time you log in with your personal customer number so in the future you will save time by not having to submit your information again. 
  2. **Traceable Product Delivery** — You will be able to track the location of your shipment through our online tracking system. 
  3. **Order Status Updates** — You will receive order status updates through email notification, including order-confirmation and order-shipped. 
  4. **Updates on Internet Specials** — You will receive updates on Internet specials you have requested, and invitations to join our Sweepstakes and giveaways. 
  5. **Personalized, Knowledgeable Customer Service** — Our customer service team will be able to assist you promptly and accurately by identifying you and your preferences. 

Kotulas.com uses a third-party service provider (Google Analytics) to collect and analyze information about our customers to better meet their needs. Google Analytics may store data or use cookies on our part, however, we do not share information that would enable them to identify you individually. Their purpose is to provide Kotulas.com with information that may better help us tailor the products and services we offer on our site. We do provide you with the opportunity to choose not to participate in the analysis of your browsing and purchasing behavior through the third-party service. For more information about our third-party service provider and how to opt out of this service, refer to the section below.

## Opting Out

You may withdraw your personal information from Kotulas.com at any time. To withdraw your information, email or write us at:

Kotula's  
Customer Service  
2800 Southcross Drive West  
PO Box 1219  
Burnsville, MN 55306-6936

## Opting Out of Third-party Services

To learn more about Adobe Marketing Cloud, their privacy policies or how to opt-out of their services, please see their [privacy overview](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html#5).

To learn more about Google Analytics, their privacy policies or how to opt-out of their services, please see their [privacy overview](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

To learn more about Criteo, their privacy policies or how to opt-out of their services, please see their [privacy overview](http://www.criteo.com/en/privacy-policy).

## Will Kotulas.com sell my email address?

NO! Kotulas.com will not sell, trade, share or rent your email address to anyone. We believe that your email address is personal and should be kept that way. We use your email address to provide you with better customer service support, and to update you on Kotulas.com Internet specials that you have requested.

If you purchase with Kotula's, we may share your information with third party catalog companies. Your name, address and details about products you have purchased from us could be shared so that you can receive catalog offers for other products that may interest you. If you would not like us to share your information for this intent, please email us or call 1-800-771-3510.

You can also write us at:  
Kotula's  
Customer Service  
2800 Southcross Drive West  
PO Box 1219  
Burnsville, MN 55306-6936
